Guide to the Dale R. Corson papers, 1935-2002.
Corson, Dale R. papers, 1963-2002.
- Series III. Research and course materials
  - Course materials
    - Physics 65, Fall Term, 1946-1947 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Physics 107 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Physics 204, 205, 206, 1948-1949 (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - Physics 393 (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Physics Lab Notes, 1947-1948 (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - Requests for Reprints, 1947-1953 (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - Publishers, 1956-1959 (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - High School Curr. Comm., 1958-1959 (Box 43, Folder 18)
    - High School Teaching, 1958 (Box 43, Folder 19)
    - High School Teaching (Box 43, Folder 20)
    - Library, 1947-1948 (Box 43, Folder 21)
    - Ithaca Schools, 1957 (Box 43, Folder 22)
    - Lincoln, 1956 (Box 43, Folder 23)
    - Nomograms (Box 43, Folder 24)
    - Physics 204-206, Spring Term, 1949 (Box 43, Folder 25)
    - Physics 206, 1948 (Box 43, Folder 26)
    - Physics 225, 1956-1957 (Box 43, Folder 27)
    - Odds and Ends (Box 43, Folder 28)
    - Orders, 1947-1953 (Box 43, Folder 29)
    - Feynmen, 1949 (Box 43, Folder 30)
    - Physics 214, 1936 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Student Notes (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - P121, 1943-1948 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Copies for DRC, 1948-1959 (Box 14, Folder 4-5)
    - P204 and 206, 1949-1951 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Physics 204 and 206, 1949-1951 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Physics 204, 1951-1952 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Physics 204, 1952 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - P225, 1951-1959 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Physics 775, 1952 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - P225 (Box 14, Folder 12-13)
    - P225 - Questionnaires (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Physics 225, 1958-1959 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Physics 225, 1953-1956 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Physics 225 - Problems, 1956 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Physics 225, 1957-1958 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Physics 225 - Problems, 1955 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Physics 225, 1952 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Physics 225, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 21-22)
    - Physics 53, 1956 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - P118, 1957 (Box 14, Folder 24-25)
    - Math (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - M220 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Teaching - Unidentified (Box 14, Folder 28-29)
    - Engineering Physics, 1955-1957 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Grad School, 1951-1954 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Physics Graduate Conference, 1955 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - E.P. Faculty Meeting Minutes, Curriculum Committee (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Baranger - Exam (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Karl Berkelman - Exam (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - Bird, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - Part A Exam - Question on the Magnetic Moment of the Neutron, M. Cohen (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - Alan Cromer - Exam, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - H. Davis - Exam, 1952 (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - B. Lipetz, 1953-1954 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - George Loeb - Exam, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Frank Loefeller - Exam (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Mark Nelkin - Exam, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - T.A. Oliphant - Exam, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Murray Peshkin - Exam, 1950 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Richard Scalettar - Exam, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - J.M. Sellen - Exam, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Part A Examination - Experimental Physics, J.M. Sellen, Jr., 1956 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - James Waggoner - Exam, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Wijnberg, 1951-1953 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - E.T. Dumitru, George Loeb, David Richman - Exams, 1957-1958 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Bruce Dalton - Correspondence and Exam (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Bruce Dalton - Research Notes (Box 15, Folder 14-15)
    - Exams (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Graduate Exams, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Series IV. Cornell administration activities
  - Physics and engineering
    - Physics Dept., Correspondence and Papers (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Physics Dept. Business (Box 15, Folder 19-23)
    - University-Corporations Relations Report (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Committee on Independent Contracts (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Dept. Chairmanship (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Butterfield, Victor (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Booker, Henry (Box 15, Folder 28-29)
    - Materials Science (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Materials Science (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Materials Science (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - University Business, 1950-1955 (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - University Business, 1950-1955 (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - ROTC (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Graduate Engineering Education (ASEE, Potsdam, NY), 1961 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Cornell academic units
    - NYS College of Ag. and Life Sciences, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - Correspondence - from Corson to Perkins re College of Ag., 1966 (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - College of Arts and Sciences, 1977-1991 (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - Biology Division, 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - School of Business and Public Administration Art Gallery, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - School of Business and Public Administration, 1981-1983 (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - Center for International Studies - Review Committee, 1990's (Box 15, Folder 43)
    - Draft Report - Corson (Box 15, Folder 44)
    - Cornell Center for the Environment, 1992-1994 (Box 15, Folder 45-46)
    - College of Engineering (Box 15, Folder 47)
    - Engineering College Council, Fall Meeting, Oct. 1999 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Cornell Society of Engineers, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Schultz Professorship - Engineering, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - E.E. Centennial Committee, 1983-1985 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Submission Structure, 1980-1981 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Charles W. Lake, Jr. Professorship, Engineering, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Engineering College Correspondence, 1988-1998 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Engineering College Correspondence, 1991-1995 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Geology, 1983-1986 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Lab of Nuclear Studies, 1980-1985 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Lab of Ornithology, 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Labor Relations, 1970-1981 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - MSC Advisory Committee, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Bard Professorship - Materials Science, 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Operations Research and Industrial Engineering, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Peace Studies, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Physics Department, 1985-1995 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Physics Major Program, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Physics Misc. (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Science and Technology - Cross Disciplinary Studies - Materials Science Center, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Science Technology and Society, 1980-1988 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Science and Technology Correspondence - Social Implications, 1988-1989 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Science and Technology - Peace Studies Program, 1988-1994 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Shoals Marine Lab, 1983-1986 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Southeast Asia Program, 1990-1991 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - SEAP Advisory Program, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Southeast Asia Program, 1991-1995 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - University committees, meetings, reports, etc.
    - Assessment of Graduate Education, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Big Four Meetings, 1978-1981 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Biological Sciences, 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - University Council, 1978-1990 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Informal Briefing Book - Materials Proposing a "New" Division for D.R. Corson, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Residential Colleges Committee Report, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Science and Technology - Task Force Committee (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Science and Technology Committee Minutes, 1988-1989 (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Committee on Social Implications of Science and Technology, Report, Apr. 11, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Events
    - Ansel Adams Lecture - Architecture, Art, and Planning, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - Al Dorskind Dinner, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - Norlander Lectures, 19880's-1990's (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Provost's Reception to Honor Cornell's New Dean and Directors, Oct. 1980 (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - Sack Lecture - F. Press, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - Mansoor I. Turki Visit, May 9, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 42)
    - Panofsky Symposium, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Awards, memorials, and other recognitions
    - Hans Bethe Events, 1980-1995 (Box 16, Folder 44)
    - Cornell Faculty - Harry Caplan, 1980-1981 (Box 16, Folder 45)
    - W. Donald Cooke, 1983-1998 (Box 16, Folder 46)
    - Mario and Manon Einaudi, 1990-1995 (Box 16, Folder 47)
    - Thomas Gold's 60th Birthday Celebration, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 48)
    - Meredith Gourdine Memorial, Feb. 12, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 49)
    - Dr. Hugh Luckey Memorial, Oct. 10, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 50)
    - Boyce McDaniel, 1987-1993 (Box 16, Folder 51)
    - Paul McKeegan, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 52)
    - John F. McManus and College of Engineering, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 53)
    - William T. Miller Service, Dec. 12, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 54)
    - Norman S. Moore Memorial, Apr. 12, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 55)
    - Floyd R. Newman Memorial, Dec. 7, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 56)
    - Spencer T. Olin Memorial, Apr. 18, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 57)
    - Don Phillips Memorial, Dec. 8, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 58)
    - Robert Purcell Union Dedication, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 59)
    - Blanchard Rideout Memorial, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 60)
    - Ed Salpeter Symposium, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 61)
    - Photographs from the Shultz and McManus Affairs, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 62)
    - Andrew Schultz Memorial Service, June 3, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 63)
    - Robert Wilson Memorial, Mar. 11, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 64)
    - Corson: George Winter Retirement, May 10, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 65)
  - Personnel
    - Cornell Eleven, 1981-1982 (Box 16, Folder 66)
    - Demas - Levitsky, 1996-1997 (Box 16, Folder 67)
    - Deane W. Malott (Box 16, Folder 68)
    - David M. Simons, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 69)
    - Endowed Professorships (Box 16, Folder 70)
    - Immigration, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 71)
    - Paul Olum, 1974-1995 (Box 16, Folder 72)
    - James Perkins (Box 16, Folder 73)
    - Provost Search, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 74)
    - Hunter Rawlings, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 75)
    - Physics - Andrei Sakharov, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 76)
  - Medical College
    - General Files (Box 16, Folder 77-78)
    - General Files (Box 16, Folder 79)
    - General Files (Box 17, Folder 1-37)
    - Deanship Search (Box 17, Folder 38-40)
    - Deanship Search (Box 18, Folder 1-2)
    - Third Century Program (Box 18, Folder 3-31)
    - Statues of Development Program (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Where Are We? (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Center Organization (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Development Office (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Untitled (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - Employee Participation (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - Third Century Case Statement (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - Contribution Report Hospital (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - Gifts, Grants, Contributions - College (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - Center Intelligence Agency (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - Third Century Program (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - Development Files (Box 18, Folder 43-44)
    - Development Files (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Solicitation Reports (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Third Century Committees (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Development Files (Box 19, Folder 4-6)
    - Corporate Gift Committees (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Estate Affairs (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Development Files (Box 19, Folder 9-15)
    - Special Events (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Direct Mail Campaign (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Development Files (Box 19, Folder 18-20)
    - Proposals (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Development Files (Box 19, Folder 22-25)
    - Cornell University - New York Hospital School of Nursing - Educational and Administrative Policy Manual, 1, 1977-1978 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Cornell University - New York Hospital School of Nursing - Educational and Administrative Policy Manual, 2, 1977-1978 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - JAB Review - 1 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - JAB Review - 2 (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - NYH-CMC Fund, Inc., Board of Dir., Agenda, June 29, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - NYH-CMC Fund, Inc., Board of Dir., Agenda, Sept. 28, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - NYH-CMC Fund, Inc., Board of Dir., Agenda, Mar. 29, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - NYH-CMC Fund, Inc., Board of Dir., Agenda, June 28, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - The Society of the New York Hospital Executive Committee Agenda, 1, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - The Society of the New York Hospital Executive Committee Agenda, 2, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - NYH-CMC JAB Agenda, May 11, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 36)
    - NYH-CMC JAB Agenda, June 29, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - NYH-CMC JAB Agenda, Sept. 28, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 38)
    - NYH-CMC JAB Agenda, Oct. 26, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 39)
    - NYH-CMC JAB Agenda, Nov. 30, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 40)
    - NYH-CMC JAB Agenda, Jan. 25, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Draft Report, Medical College, 1 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Draft Report, Medical College, 2 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - NYH-CMC JAB Agenda, Mar. 29, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - NYH-CMC JAB Agenda, Apr. 26, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - NYH-CMC JAB Agenda, May 31, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - NYH-CMC JAB Agenda, June 28, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - NYH-CMC, The Report of the Ad Hoc Committee on Capital Financing and Financial Planning, Dec. 1975 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Review of NYC-CU Joint Agreement (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Financial History of the NYC-CMC (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Report of the Dean - Cornell University Medical College, June 30, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Deinert Letter (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Special Letters (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - LPW - Dannhauser (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Radiology - Department Reviews (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Obstetrics and Gynecology - Departmental Review (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - JAB - Review, 1 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - JAB - Review, 2 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - JAB Review Committee Papers, Nov. 19, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - JAB Review (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Comm. on Capital Financing and Financial Planning (Box 20, Folder 21-24)
    - Council on Higher Education in the American Republics (Box 20, Folder 25-27)
    - Executive Faculty Council (Box 20, Folder 28-33)
    - General Faculty Council (Box 20, Folder 34-38)
    - Development Files (Box 20, Folder 39-40)
    - Development Files (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Sloan-Kettering 1979 Directory of Officers and Board Members, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - NY Hospital Board of Governors (Box 21, Folder 3-11)
    - Weiss Committee on the Health Sciences (Box 21, Folder 12-14)
    - Med. College, Correspondence (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Cornell Med. Coll., "Desegregating Medical Education - The Quiet Revolution," by James L. Curtis, M.D., Part 1 - 1 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Cornell Med. Coll., "Desegregating Medical Education - The Quiet Revolution," by James L. Curtis, M.D., Part 1 - 2 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Cornell Med. Coll., "Desegregating Medical Education…" Part 2 - The Message of Change, 1 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Cornell Med. Coll., "Desegregating Medical Education…" Part 2 - The Message of Change, 2 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Medical College, NY Hospital (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - CUMC-NYH Symposium Honoring Eleanor C. Lambertsen, June 23, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Merger, New Medical School (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - CUMC (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Vicent du Vigneaud Memorial (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Sloan-Kettering (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Sloan-Kettering Inst. (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Trustees
    - Correspondence, General, 1878-1981 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Speech - State of the University to Trustees, June 2, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Background Material, 1973-1977 (Box 21, Folder 29-30)
    - Background Material, 1973-1978 (Box 21, Folder 31-32)
    - Board Report - 1, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - "Seven Springs" Report (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - Board Report - 2, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - Trustees/Council Weekend, Oct. 19-21, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - Proceedings - 1, 1978-1979 (Box 21, Folder 37)
    - Proceedings - 2, 1978-1979 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Board of Trustees, 1978-1979 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Executive Committee, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Development Advisory Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Members of the Board of Trustees (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Board of Trustees, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Board of Trustees, 1980-1981 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Board of Trustees - Proceedings, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Board of Trustees, 1981-1982 (Box 22, Folder 9-10)
    - CU Board Meeting, May 29, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Board of Trustees, 1982-1984 (Box 22, Folder 12-13)
    - Board of Trustees, 1983-1984 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Board of Trustees, 1983, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Trustee Dinner Honoring DMC, May 28, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Development and corporate relations
    - Statement of Gift Policy (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Assignments, 1978-1979 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Advisory Committee, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Advisory Committee, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Advisory Committee, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Cornell Fund (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Advisory Committee, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Minimum Levels for Endowment (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Advisory Committee Meting, May 30, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 22, Folder 26-27)
    - Markoe, Frank Jr. - Medical College (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Corson's Trip to Florida, Mar.-Apr. 1981 (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - Mr. and Mrs. Corson, Florida, Feb. 13-22, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Bendix, GM, Detroit Edison, Oct. 15, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - Professor Scheinman's Visit to Japan (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - Boston, Oct. 1977 (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - Dale R. Corson, Cleveland Visit, Sept. 26, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - Florida, Feb. 19, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - Tokyo Trip, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - Japan/China Travel and Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - Hawaii, 1976-1977 (Box 22, Folder 38)
    - Western Trip, Apr. 1978 (Box 22, Folder 39)
    - Chicago, May 1978 (Box 22, Folder 40)
    - Florida, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 41)
    - Meeting - Robert Hays, Mar. 1978 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Tim Perkins Dinner, Mar. 1978 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Meeting - Herbert Hubben Eaton Corporation, Mar. 1978 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Meeting - F.R. Newman, Mar. 1978 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Meeting - John W. Reavis, Mar. 1978 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Meeting - Corporate Representatives, Cleveland, Mar. 1978 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Meeting - Midland - Ross Corporation, Mar. 1978 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Meeting with J.D. Ireland, Cleveland, Mar. 1978 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Itinerary, Florida Trip, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Dinner - Marie Noll, Florida Trip, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Investment Committee Meeting, Florida Trip, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Meeting - Mr. and Mrs. L. Sevringhaus, Florida Trip, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Gift Correspondence (Other than Music) (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Cornell Campaign Advertisement (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Dyson Gift - Institute for Socio-Economic Studies (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Cornell Campaign (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Cornell University Southeast Regional Office (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Submicron Facility (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Major Gifts Committee Meeting, Dec. 6, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Major Gifts Committee (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Dinner in Honor of Al Saperston, Apr. 5, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Class of 1950, Reunion 1980, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Class of 1969 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Alumni News (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Alumni Reunions (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - 1989 Reunion - Class of 1919 (70th), 1989 (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Class Reunions 1981, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - Reunion 1985, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - Reunion 1984, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - Reunion 1983, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - Reunion 1982, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - Alumni Relations (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - Allegheny Ludlum Industries, Inc. (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - Amsted Industries (Box 23, Folder 35)
    - ARCO (Box 23, Folder 36)
    - American Electric Power (Box 23, Folder 37)
    - Bausch and Lomb, Dec. 6, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 38)
    - Bendix (Box 23, Folder 39)
    - Bethlehem Steel Corp. (Box 23, Folder 40)
    - FMC Corp. (Box 23, Folder 41)
    - GATX Corp. (Box 23, Folder 42)
    - General Electric (Box 23, Folder 43)
    - The General Foods Fund, Inc. (Box 23, Folder 44)
    - Gulf Oil Foundation (Box 23, Folder 45)
    - W.R. Grace (Box 23, Folder 46)
    - Meeting with D.S. Potter - General Motors, Oct. 15, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 47)
    - Gould Pumps (Box 23, Folder 48)
    - Borg-Warner Corp. (Box 23, Folder 49)
    - Burroughs Corp. (Box 23, Folder 50)
    - Cargill Inc. (Box 23, Folder 51)
    - Chemetron Corp. (Box 23, Folder 52)
    - Chevron (Box 23, Folder 53)
    - Chicago Bridge and Iron (Box 23, Folder 54)
    - Crown Zellerbach (Box 23, Folder 55)
    - R.R. Donnelley and Sons Co. (Box 23, Folder 56)
    - Dow Chemical U.S.A. (Box 23, Folder 57)
    - Esmark, Conatiner Corp. of America, G.D. Searle, Signode (Box 23, Folder 58)
    - Hewlett Packard (Box 23, Folder 59)
    - IMC (Box 23, Folder 60)
    - Inland Steel (Box 23, Folder 61)
    - Intel (Box 23, Folder 62)
    - International Paper Co. (Box 23, Folder 63)
    - Kraft, Inc. (Box 23, Folder 64)
    - Kodak (Box 23, Folder 65)
    - Lukens Steel, Whitney Mullestein (Box 23, Folder 66)
    - Marcel Breuer Associates (Box 23, Folder 67)
    - McGraw-Edison Co. (Box 23, Folder 68)
    - Nalco Chemical Co. (Box 23, Folder 69)
    - National Semiconductor (Box 23, Folder 70)
    - NYSEG (Box 23, Folder 71)
    - Perkins and Will (Box 23, Folder 72)
    - Quaker Oats (Box 23, Folder 73)
    - Standard Oil of Indiana (Box 23, Folder 74)
    - Sybron Corporation (Box 23, Folder 75)
    - Sperry Rand (Box 23, Folder 76)
    - Standard Oil of California (Box 23, Folder 77)
    - Chevron (Box 23, Folder 78)
    - Standard Oil of Ohio (Box 23, Folder 79)
    - Times Mirror (Box 23, Folder 80)
    - WARF (Box 23, Folder 81)
    - Watkins Johnson (Box 23, Folder 82)
    - Whitco Chemical Corp. (Box 23, Folder 83)
    - Whitco Chemical (Box 23, Folder 84)
    - Zurn (Box 23, Folder 85)
    - Corp. Relations Misc. (Box 23, Folder 86)
    - National Corporate Gifts, July 12, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 87)
    - Alger Dedication and Letters (Box 23, Folder 88)
    - Phoebe Bard Boand (Box 23, Folder 89)
    - Herbert E. Carnes Fund (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Carpenter, Walter Samuel Jr. (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Clark, C. Paul (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Clark Family (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Collyer, Mr. and Mrs. John (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Cooley, Carolyn (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Coors, Joe (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Cornell, Mrs. Hallis E. (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Davidson, Norman (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Davis, Nelson (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Dean, Mrs. Arther H. (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Gift Fellowship Fund (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Grumman, David (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Grumman, Leroy R. (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Hooker, Wolcott (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Hopkins, Henry (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Hales, Mr. and Mrs. N. Battle (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Johnson, H. F. (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Johnson, S.C. - 1 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Johnson, S.C. - 2 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Johnston, F.A. (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - John Knight and Knight Foundation (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Meeting with John Knight, Feb. 16, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Knight, L.B. (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Kraft (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Lewis, Mr. and Mrs. Thomas E. (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Mellows, Charles (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - McAdam, Sr., Charles V (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - McLain, N.H. (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Newman, F.R. (Box 24, Folder 30)